Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen Records 5148
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen Records
1910-1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen (ORC&B)
5148
22.44 cubic feet
22.4 linear ft.
Memorabilia, photographs.
These records represent the small surviving fraction of the union's total record production, the largest part of which was periodically disposed of throughout the history of the union.
3336753
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 21, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 07, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen (ORC & B) was founded in 1868 as an order of railroad conductors and later expanded to include brakemen.
The Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen was founded by T.J. "Tommie" Wright in 1868 in Amboy, Ill. as the Conductors Union. The name was changed to Order of Railway Conductors of America (ORC) in 1878. In 1942, the Order of Sleeping Car Conductors merged with ORC. The union's name was changed in 1954 to the Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen. In 1969, the Order merged with the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, and Switchmen's Union of North America to form the United Transportation Union.
The ORC & B International Headquarters, Grand Division, was located in Cedar Rapids, Iowa with subordinate divisions in the United States, Canada, and the Panama Canal Zone. The principal officers included the president, senior vice-president, general secretary-treasurer, executive vice-president, vice-president/Washington legislative representative, vice-president/National Railroad Adjustment Board, four regional vice-presidents, Board of Trustees (3 members), and the ORC & B Board of Directors (comprised of the above 13 officers.) General Adjustment Committees on each property (Class 1 railroads) were responsible for execution of the contract, with each chairman, as principal officer, exercising a high degree of autonomy. Legislative matters on the state level were the responsibility of the State Legislative Committee and its chairman.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5148 MB: Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen Memorabilia 5148 P: Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen Photographs 5754: Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen and Seaboard Airline Railroad Company General Committee of Adjustment Files 6289: Order of Railway Conductors Division 642 Records
Arbitration, Industrial -- Railroads -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Railroads -- United States; Grievance procedures -- Railroads -- United States; Hours of labor -- Railroads -- United States; Accident insurance -- United States; Labor disputes -- Railroads -- United States; Labor productivity -- Railroads -- United States; Mediation and conciliation, Industrial -- Railroads -- United States; Nationalization -- Railroads -- United States; Railroad brakemen -- United States; Railroad employees -- United States -- Registers; Railroads -- Industrial relations -- United States; Railroads -- Accidents -- United States; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- United States; Railroads -- Safety appliances -- United States; Railroads -- United States -- State supervision; Wages -- Railraods -- United States; Retirement -- Railroads -- United States; Strikes and lockouts -- Railroads -- United States; Labor union insurance -- United States; Labor unions -- Mergers -- United States; Trade-union rituals.; Union solidarity -- United States; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- California -- San Francisco; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States -- Labor union locals; Labor unions -- United States -- Local unions; Work rules -- Railroads -- United States; Labor laws and legislation-United States.; Railroad conductors-United States.; Railroads -- Employees; Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway Company; Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company; Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company; Bangor and Aroostook Railroad Company; Boston and Albany Railroad Co.; Boston and Maine Railroad; Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.); Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; Burlington and Rock Island Railroad; Central of Georgia Railroad Company; Central of New Jersey Railroad Company; Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad Company; Chicago & Eastern Illinois Railroad Company; Chicago and North Western Railway Company; Chicago, Burlington & Quincy Railroad Company; Chicago Great Western Railway Company (1940-1968); Chicago, Indianapolis & Louisville Railway Company; Chicago, Milwaukee, and St. Paul Railway Company; Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad Company (1948- ); Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad Company; Gulf, Mobile and Ohio Railroad Company; Illinois Central Railroad Company; Kansas City Southern Railway Company; Lehigh and New England Railroad; Lehigh Valley Railroad Company; Long Island Rail Road; Louisville and Nashville Railroad Company; Maine Central Railroad Company; Michigan Central Railroad Company; Minneapolis & St. Louis Railroad; Minneapolis &St. Paul Railroad; Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad; Missouri Pacific Railroad Company; Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway; New Orleans and Northeastern Railroad; New York Central and Hartford Railroad; New York Central Railroad Company; Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen; Order of Railway Conductors of America; Southern Pacific Company; United States. National Railroad Adjustment Board; United Trainmen's Association; Bendestet, Karl R.; Bennett, Paul R.; Clark, E. E.; Daniels, William P.; Debs, Eugene V. (Eugene Victor), 1855-1926.; Fraser, Harry W.; Garretson, Austin B.; Hughes, Roy O.; Kalka, J. F.; Knox, Philander C. (Philander Chase), 1853-1921; Lundborg, O. R.; McDonough, John C.; Moseley, Ned, 1846-1911; Niles, J. O.; Paddock, J. A.; Richard, J.K.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945; Shelly, Kate; Sheppard, L. E.; Wagner, Louis J.; Wheaton, C. S.; Willkie, Wendell L. (Wendell Lewis), 1892-1944
3336753
- Constitutions, 1881-1919 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Constitutions, 1881-1919 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Constitutions, 1881-1919 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Constitutions, 1881-1919 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Constitutions, 1922-1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Constitutions, 1920-1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Constitutions, 1920-1941 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Constitutions, 1920-1941 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Constitutions, 1946-1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Constitutions, 1946-1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Constitutions, 1946-1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Grand Lodge Exec. Comm. Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Scope and Contents
  January 1951 - May 1952
- Grand Lodge Exec. Comm. Minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Grand Lodge Exec. Comm. Minutes, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Grand Lodge Exec. Comm. Minutes, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Grand Lodge Exec. Comm. Minutes, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Grand Lodge Exec. Comm. Minutes, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Grand Lodge Exec. Comm. Minutes, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Grand Chief Conductor C. S. Wheaton, 1880-1890 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Grand Chief Conductor E. E. Clark, 1890-1906 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Grand Chief Conductor E. E. Clark - Olmstead File, 1890-1906 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- A. B. Garretson, 1906-1919 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  President A. B. Garretson 1906-1907, President A. B. Garretson 1907-1919
- Grand Lodge Executive Comm. Minutes, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Grand Lodge Executive Comm. Minutes, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Grand Lodge Executive Comm. Minutes, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Grand Lodge Executive Comm. Minutes, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Grand Lodge Executive Comm. Minutes, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- President J. A. Phillips - Correspondence, 1935-1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- President H. W. Fraser, 1941-1950 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Hughes & Re Hughes, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- J. A. Phillips - Correspondence concerning proposed book, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- J. A. Phillips - Correspondence concerning proposed book, 1940-1943 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- J. A. Phillips - Material file for his proposed book, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- President R. O. Hughes, 1950-1958 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- President L. J. Wagner, 1961-1964 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Paddock - Misc., 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Paddock - Misc., 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Paddock - Misc. (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Paddock - Misc., 1922-1966 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Sec. Treasurer Bermuda Plantation - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Minutes of Gen. Chairmen, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Fin. Rpt., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Secretary Treasurer ORC Corporation, 1889-1937 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- ORC Minutes, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- ORC - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Nat'l Bank of Commerce - Ledger, 1906-1918 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- ORC Terminal City Div. No. 269 - Ledger, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Minutes - General Chairmen's Meetings, 1958-1968 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  Binder
- Atlantic Coast Lines, 1909-1942 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Atlantic Coast Lines, 1944-1947 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Atlantic Coast Lines, 1948-1953 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Atlantic Coast Lines, 1953-1965 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- A. T. & S. F., 1907-1946 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- A. T. & S. F., 1947-1952 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- A. T. & S. F., 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- A. T. & S. F., 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- A. T. & S. F., 1957 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- A. T. & S. F., 1958 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- A. T. & S. F., 1960 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- A. T. & S. F. Coast Lines, 1918-1929 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- A. T. & S. F. Coast Lines, 1932-1946 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- A. T. & S. F. Coast Lines, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- A. T. & S. F. Coast Lines, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- A. T. & S. F. Coast Lines, 1952-1955 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- A. T. & S. F. Coast Lines, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- A. T. & S. F. Coast Lines, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- A. T. & S. F. Coast Lines, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- A. T. & S. F. Coast Lines, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Gulf Coast & Santa Fe, 1908-1941 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Gulf Coast & Santa Fe, 1944-1948 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Gulf Coast & Santa Fe, 1949-1955 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Gulf Coast & Santa Fe, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Atlantic & West Point, 1911-1955 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Baltimore & Ohio, 1910-1947 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Baltimore & Ohio, 1948-1950 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Baltimore & Ohio, 1953-1956 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Baltimore & Ohio, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Baltimore & Ohio, 1957-1961 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Bangor & Aroostook, 1907-1919 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Boston & Albany, 1908-1944 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Boston & Albany, 1946-1962 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Boston & Maine, 1911-1932 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Boston & Maine, 1942-1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Burlington & Rock Island, 1945-1952 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Central of Georgia, 1918-1940 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Central of Georgia, 1944-1947 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Central of Georgia, 1949-1954 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Central of Georgia, 1956-1963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Central of New Jersey, 1917-1949 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Central of New Jersey, 1951-1961 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Lehigh & New England [co. of NJ Lines], 1952-1958 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Chesapeake & Ohio, 1910-1935 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Chesapeake & Ohio, 1938-1944 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Chesapeake & Ohio, 1946-1953 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Chesapeake & Ohio, 1953-1957 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- C&O Pere Marquette, 1920-1945 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- C&O Pere Marquette, 1946-1957 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Hocking Valley [C. & O. Lines], 1945 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Chicago, Burlington & Quincy, 1908-1929 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Chicago, Burlington & Quincy, 1932-1942 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Chicago, Burlington & Quincy, 1945-1947 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Chicago, Burlington & Quincy, 1948-1953 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Chicago, Burlington & Quincy, 1953-1956 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Chicago, Burlington & Quincy, 1957-1961 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Chicago, Burlington & Quincy, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Chicago & Eastern Illinois, 1939-1947 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Chicago Great Western, 1912-1949 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Chicago, Indianapolis & Louisville (Monon R.R.), 1907-1962 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- C. M. St. P. & P. (Lines East), 1908-1919 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- C. M. St. P. & P. (Lines East), 1924-1940 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- C. M. St. P. & P. (Lines East), 1945-1948 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- C. M. St. P. & P. (Lines East), 1949-1953 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- C. M. St. P. & P. (Lines East), 1957-1959 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- C. M. St. P. & P. (Lines West), 1914-1933 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- C. M. St. P. & P. (Lines West), 1935-1942 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- C. M. St. P. & P. (Lines West), 1944-1949 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- C. M. St. P. & P. (Lines West), 1953-1957 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Chicago & Northwestern, 1903-1920 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Chicago & Northwestern, 1926-1942 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Chicago & Northwestern, 1942-1952 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Chicago & Northwestern, 1952-1954 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Chicago & Northwestern, 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Chicago & Northwestern, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Chicago & Northwestern, 1957-1961 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Chicago, Rock Island & Pacific, 1904-1935 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- C. RI & P., 1942-1946 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- C. RI & P., 1949 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- C. RI & P., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- C. RI & P., 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- C. RI & P., 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- C. RI & P., 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- C. C. C. & St. L., 1910-1928 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- C. C. C. & St. L., 1932-1939 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- C. C. C. & St. L., 1942-1949 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- C. C. C. & St. L., 1950-1956 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- C. C. C. & St. L., 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Gulf, Mobile & Ohio [Northern], 1921-1936 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Gulf, Mobile & Ohio [Northern], 1940-1946 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Gulf, Mobile & Ohio [Northern], 1952-1957 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Gulf, Mobile & Ohio [Southern], 1942 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Gulf, Mobile & Ohio [Southern], 1944-1949 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Gulf, Mobile & Ohio [Southern], 1954-1962 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Illinois Central, 1930-1948 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Illinois Central, 1948-1950 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Illinois Central, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Illinois Central, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Illinois Central, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Illinois Central, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Illinois Central, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Illinois Central, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Illinois Central, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Kansas City Southern, 1920-1942 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Kansas City Southern, 1945-1952 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Kansas City Southern, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Kansas City Southern, 1955-1960 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Lehigh Valley, 1947-1954 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Lehigh Valley, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Long Island RR, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Louisville & Nashville, 1919-1946 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- L. & N. RR, 1946-1951 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- L. & N. RR, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- L. & N. RR, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- L. & N. RR, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- L. & N. RR, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- L. & N. RR, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Maine Central, 1932-1949 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Michigan Central, 1944-1961 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Minneapolis & St. Louis, 1936-1957 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- M. St. P. & S. S. M. [500 Line], 1907-1948 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- M. St. P. & S. S. M. [500 Line], 1949-1955 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- M. St. P. & S. S. M. [500 Line], 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Missouri - Kansas - Texas, 1918-1935 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Missouri - Kansas - Texas, 1944-1952 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Missouri - Kansas - Texas, 1956-1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Missouri Pacific [Proper], 1904-1945 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Missouri Pacific [Proper], 1948 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Missouri Pacific [Proper], 1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Missouri Pacific [Proper], 1957-1961 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Missouri Pacific [Gulf Coast Lines], 1908-1920 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- MO Pac. [Gulf Coast Lines], 1927-1937 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- MO Pac. [Gulf Coast Lines], 1941-1949 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- MO Pac. [Gulf Coast Lines], 1952-1954 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- MO Pac. [Gulf Coast Lines], 1955-1959 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- New Orleans & Northeastern Railroad Co., 1926-1928 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- New Orleans & Northeastern Railroad Co., 1926-1928 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- New Orleans & Northeastern RR Co., 1926-1928 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- New Orleans & Northeastern RR Co., 1926-1928 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Local 1 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Local 18 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Local 20 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Local 23 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Local 25 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Local 28 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Local 30 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Local 31 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Local 32 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Local 33 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Local 34 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Local 36 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Local 38 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Local 42 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Local 43 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Local 44 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Local 45 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Local 46 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Local 49 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Local 50 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Local 51 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Local 52 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Local 53 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Local 54 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Local 56 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Local 63 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Local 64 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Local 65 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Local 83 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Local 87 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Local 98 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Local 99 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Local 101 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Local 102 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Local 103 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Local 104 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Local 105 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Local 106 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Local 107 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Local 109 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Local 110 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Local 111 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Local 19 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Local 26 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Local 40 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Local 100 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Register of Divisions - Order of Railway Conductors (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Large Ledger
- Record - Minutes, 1903-1909 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Ledger - November 21, 1903 to December 31, 1909
- Members, 1906-1923 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Ledger
- Ledger O. R. C., 1892-1894 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Ledger O. R. C., 1895-1900 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Ledger O. R. C., 1906-1909 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Ledger O. R. C., 1910-1911 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Ledger O. R. C., 1912-1914 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Ledger, 1913-1914 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Ledger, 1916-1917 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Ledger, 1918-1920 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Ledger O. R. C., 1920 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Ledger, 1920-1922 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Ledger, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Record, 1926-1927 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Ledger O. R. C., 1930-1931 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Ledger O. R. C., 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Ledger O. R. C., 1935-1936 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Ledger O. R. C., 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Ledger O. R. C., 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Ledger O. R. C., 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Ledger O. R. C., 1943 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Ledger O. R. C., 1945 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Cash Book O. R. C., 1940-1943 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Cash Book O. R. C., 1944-1947 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Cash Book O. R. C., 1948-1952 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Cash Book O. R. C., 1953-1955 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Cash Book O. R. C., 1963-1967 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Ledger, 1965-1969 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Local 151 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Local 152 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Local 153 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Local 154 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Local 155 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Local 156 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Local 157 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Local 158 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Local 160 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Local 161 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Local 162 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Local 164 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Local 165 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Local 166 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Local 168 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Local 169 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Local 170 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Local 172 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Local 174 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Local 175 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Local 177 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Local 180 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Local 181 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Local 182 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Local 185 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Local 186 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Local 187 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Local 192 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Local 193 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Local 196 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Local 198 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Local 203 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Local 204 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Local 205 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Local 206 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Local 207 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Local 209 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Local 210 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Local 211 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Local 213 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Local 217 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Local 218 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Local 220 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Local 223 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Local 224 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Local 225 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Local 226 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Local 229 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Local 231 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Local 232 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Local 234 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Local 235 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Local 241 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Local 243 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Local 244 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- Local 249 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- Local 251 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Local 253 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- Local 256 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- Local 257 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- Local 258 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- Local 259 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- Local 261 (Box 12, Folder 63)
- Local 262 (Box 12, Folder 64)
- Local 263 (Box 12, Folder 65)
- Local 264 (Box 12, Folder 66)
- Local 267 (Box 12, Folder 67)
- Local 270 (Box 12, Folder 68)
- Local 271 (Box 12, Folder 69)
- Local 275 (Box 12, Folder 70)
- Local 278 (Box 12, Folder 71)
- Local 281 (Box 12, Folder 72)
- Local 282 (Box 12, Folder 73)
- Local 284 (Box 12, Folder 74)
- Local 285 (Box 12, Folder 75)
- Local 289 (Box 12, Folder 76)
- Local 290 (Box 12, Folder 77)
- Local 292 (Box 12, Folder 78)
- Local 293 (Box 12, Folder 79)
- Local 299 (Box 12, Folder 80)
- Local 300 (Box 12, Folder 81)
- Local 301 (Box 12, Folder 82)
- Local 302 (Box 12, Folder 83)
- Local 303 (Box 12, Folder 84)
- Local 307 (Box 12, Folder 85)
- Local 308 (Box 12, Folder 86)
- Local 309 (Box 12, Folder 87)
- Local 311 (Box 12, Folder 88)
- Local 312 (Box 12, Folder 89)
- Local 314 (Box 12, Folder 90)
- Local 316 (Box 12, Folder 91)
- Local 317 (Box 12, Folder 92)
- Local 318 (Box 12, Folder 93)
- Local 320 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Local 321 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Local 324 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Local 326 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Local 327 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Local 328 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Local 329 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Local 331 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Local 334 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Local 335 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Local 339 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Local 340 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Local 347 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Local 350 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Local 351 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Local 354 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Local 356 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Local 357 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Local 359 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Local 360 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Local 365 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Local 370 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Local 373 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Local 374 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Local 375 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Local 378 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Local 379 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Local 380 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Local 381 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Local 382 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Local 384 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Local 386 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Local 391 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Local 392 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Local 395 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Local 397 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Local 399 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Local 401 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Local 402 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Local 403 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Local 404 (Box 13, Folder 41)